Finding Aid for the Jon Krampner Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- “Q”
  - Site Files
    - Oconee County (1-34 plus 1 page) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Cherokee County (1-19) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Asheville (1-5 and 9-10) (Box 7, File 5, Folder 11)
    - Houston, Mississippi (1-25) (Box 7, File 5, Folder 12)
    - Empty (Box 7, File 5, Folder 13)
    - Memphis (1-18 plus 3 pages) (Box 7, File 5, Folder 14)
    - Memphis Pix (1-21) (Box 7, File 6, Folder 15)
    - The Delta (Mississippi) (1-14 and 19-31 plus 1 page) (Box 7, File 6, Folder 16)
    - Buckhorn (1-3 and 6-42 plus 1 page) (Box 7, File 7, Folder 17)
- “R”
  - 2 pages of outline
    - Demonstration School Class Pix (1-9) (Box 7, File 8, Folder 1)
    - Play Lists (1-32) (Box 7, File 8, Folder 2)
    - Nashville- General (1-27) (Box 7, File 8, Folder 3)
    - Nashville Pix (1-14) (Box 7, File 9, Folder 4)
    - Fred Coe Domiciles (1-4) (Box 7, File 9, Folder 5)
    - Joseph Udelson (1-2) (Box 7, File 9, Folder 6)
    - Group Meeting (1-8) (Box 7, File 9, Folder 7)
    - Jeanne Bodfish (1-35) (Box 7, File 9, Folder 8)
    - Spiller Campbell (1-6) (Box 7, File 10, Folder 9)
    - Richard Dunn (1-4) (Box 7, File 10, Folder 10)
    - Era Fisher 1-2) (Box 7, File 10, Folder 11)
    - Fred Fisher (1) (Box 7, File 10, Folder 12)
    - Jane Geistman (Mrs. Goodall Bailey) (1-12) (Box 7, File 10, Folder 13)
    - Martha Geistman (Mrs. Colin Campbell) (1-11) (Box 7, File 10, Folder 14)
    - Casper Kuhn (Dick Dudley) (1-19) (Box 7, File 10, Folder 15)
    - Martha Lane Tippens (1) (Box 7, File 11, Folder 16)
    - Delbert Mann (1-9) (Box 7, File 11, Folder 17)
    - Don Phillips and Andrina Phillips (1-41) (Box 7, File 11, Folder 18)
    - Marianne Smith (1-2) (Box 7, File 12, Folder 19)
    - Max Souby (1-11) (Box 7, File 12, Folder 20)
    - Nashville News Clips (1-16) (Box 7, File 12, Folder 21)
    - A. E. Oscar Wright (1-3) (Box 7, File 12, Folder 22)
    - Primordial TV (1-2) (Box 7, File 12, Folder 23)
- “S”
  - Yale
    - General (1-18) (Box 7, File 13, Folder 1)
    - Yale Drama—Playbills (1-28) (Box 7, File 13, Folder 2)
    - Melville H. Bernstein (1-2) (Box 7, File 13, Folder 3)
    - Henry M. Bluestone (1-2) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 4)
    - Sarah (Click) Ferry (1-3) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 5)
    - Marshall Jamison (1-2) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 6)
    - Don Haldane (1-2) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 7)
    - Adna Karns (1-4) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 8)
    - Henry Klopot (1-4) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 9)
    - Margaret Oakley (Daisy Pickhaw) (1) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 10)
    - Otto Preminger (1-3) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 11)
    - Margaret (Thomson) Jones (1-3) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 12)
  - Columbia, South Carolina
    - General (1-7) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 13)
    - Columbia, South Carolina, Pix (1-10) (Box 8, File 1, Folder 14)
    - Town Theatre- Master’s Thesis (1-14) (Box 8, File 2, Folder 15)
    - Town Theatre- Articles and Reviews (1-63 plus 1 page) (Box 8, File 2, Folder 16)
    - Vera (Bihari) Roukos (1-3) (Box 8, File 3, Folder 17)
    - Joe (David) Bishop (1-3) (Box 8, File 3, Folder 18)
    - Jo(sephine) Brown (1-17) (Box 8, File 3, Folder 19)
    - Robert Bullock (1-2) (Box 8, File 3, Folder 20)
    - Dr. George Curry (1-4) (Box 8, File 3, Folder 21)
    - Jennie (Dreher) Evins (1) (Box 8, File 3, Folder 22)
    - Albert Eggerton (1-4) (Box 8, File 3, Folder 23)
    - Charles Wickenberg (1-22) (Box 8, File 4, Folder 24)
    - Caroline (Le Caru ) Judson (1-4) (Box 8, File 4, Folder 25)
    - Allen Whitehead (1-7) (Box 8, File 4, Folder 26)
  - Etc.
    - Faulkner Quotes ( 9 pages) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Philco Listings
    - Summary (22 pages) (Box 8, File 5)
    - (24 pages) (Box 8, Folder 1949)
    - (46 pages) (Box 8, Folder 1950)
    - (55 pages) (Box 8, File 6, Folder 1951)
    - (52 pages) (Box 8, File 6, Folder 1952)
    - (53 pages) (Box 8, File 7, Folder 1953)
    - (46 pages) (Box 8, Folder 1954)
    - (11 pages) (Box 8, Folder 1955)
  - Fred Coe Teleplays
    - Something in the Wind (13 pages) (Box 8, File 8)
    - This Time Next Year (1-8 plus 102 pages) (Box 8, File 9)
  - Alice
    - Alice—Gen. (1-6 plus 6 pages) (Box 8, File 10)
    - A-5 (Bookshop) (1-10) (Box 8, File 10)
    - B-15 (Chap.5) (1-49 and 57-60) (Box 8, File 10)
    - D-13 (Chap.3) (1-30) (Box 8, File 11)
    - F-3 (Chap.4) (1-21) (Box 8, File 11)
    - I-3 (Chap.6) (1-51 plus 3 pages) (Box 8, File 12)
    - M (Chap. 8) (1-28) (Box 8, File 13)
    - FC Letters to AC (1-11 plus 2 pages) (Box 8, File 13)
  - Joyce
    - Bellevue Trip (1-22) [Bellevue, Iowa] (Box 9, File 1)
    - A-6 (Book Group) (1-10) (Box 9, File 1)
    - B-16 (Chapter 5) (1-19 Plus 1 page) (Box 9, File 1)
    - F-4 (Chapter 4) (1-72) (Box 9, File 2)
    - I-4 (Chapter 6) (1-22) \ (Box 9, File 3)
    - “Peepers” Expense Reports (1-3 plus 3 pages) (Box 9, File 3)
    - Robert “Bob” Sunday (1-3 plus 1 page) (Box 9, File 3)
    - Sorority Sisters (1-22) (Box 9, File 3)
    - 1067 Fifth Ave (Box 9, File 3)
    - Miscellaneous Materials (File 4)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Materials found loose in binders (Box 9, File 5)
    - FC’s Address Book (Box 9, File 6)
    - Nashville Days (Kate Wells) (Box 9, File 7)
    - FC “12 Nite” Note to Del (Box 9, File 8)
    - Reviews, Etc. (Box 9, File 9)
  - Photos
    - Photos From Book (Box 9, File 10)
    - Photos From Book (Box 9, File 11)
    - Photos From Book (Box 9, File 12)
  - Videos
    - Video- Remembering Fred Coe: “The Live Television Years” (Box 9, File 13)
    - Video- A Tribute to Fred Coe- Museum of T.V. and Radio Paley Festival Los Angeles 3/2000 (Box 9, File 13)
    - Video- T:53188 A Tribute to Fred Coe TRT: 01:33:54 VHS Copy-With Clips Seminar, 5/14/98 (Box 9, File 13)
  - Cassette Tapes
    - Martin Manulis 7/19/93 (#2) (Box 1, Folder A)
    - E. Hotchner, 2/2/94 (Box 1, Folder A)
    - Ira Skutch, 2/24/93 (Box 1, Folder B)
    - Delbert Mann, 2/18/93 (Box 2, Folder A)
    - Rose Claire Duff, 2/25/93 (Box 2, Folder A)
    - Bob Costello, 2/25/93 (Box 2, Folder A)
    - Jeanne Bodfish, 2/25/93 (Box 2, Folder A)
    - Jeanne Bodfish, 2/25/93 (Box 2, Folder B)
    - Tad Mosel, 2/2/94 (Box 2, Folder B)
    - Phyllis Jenkins, 2/2/94 (Box 2, Folder B)
    - Ellen Violett, 2/3/94 (Box 2, Folder B)
    - Name scratched out, 2/2/94 (Box 3, Folder A)
    - 3-B Pat Weaver, 3/3/93 (Box 3, Folder A)
    - Alice Coe: Fred’s (something illegible) (Box 3, Folder A)
    - Alice Coe, 2/19/93 (Box 4, Folder B)
    - Alice Coe (Box 4, Folder B)
    - Martin Manulis, 7/19/93 (Box 4, Folder B)
    - Names scratched out (Box 5, Folder A)
    - Delbert Mann, 3/3/93 (Box 5, Folder B)
    - (Name Illegible), 3/3/93 (Box 5, Folder B)
    - Old Del, Arthur P. ints (Box 5, Folder B)
    - Marshall Jamison, Adna Karns, 2/22/93 (Box 6, Folder A)
    - Delbert Mann, 1/31/94 (Box 6, Folder A)
    - Delbert Mann 1/31/94 (jump), 2/2/94 (Box 6, Folder B)
    - David Karp 2/1/94 (jump from #4) (Box 6, Folder B)
    - J. P. Miller, 2/2/94 (Box 6, Folder B)
    - Arthur Penn, 2/2/94 (Box 6, Folder B)
    - Names scratched out, 2/2/94 (Box 7, Folder A)
    - Alice Coe, 3/5/93 (Box 7, Folder B)
    - Names scratched out (Box 8, Folder A)
    - Don Phillips, 4/12/93 (Box 8, Folder B)
    - Names scratched out (Box 9, Folder A)
    - Names scratched out (Box 9, Folder B)
    - 10-A John Bloch, 4/14/93 (Box 10, Folder A)
    - Brooks Graham, 4/15/93 (Box 10, Folder A)
    - Charles Cappelman, 4/15/93 (Box 10, Folder A)
    - Mrs. Goodall Bailey (Jane Geistman), 4/20/93 (Box 10, Folder A)
    - Richard Dunn, 4/13/93 (Box 10, Folder B)
    - Dick Dudley, 4/13/93 (Box 10, Folder B)
    - John Bloch, 4/13/93 (Box 10, Folder B)
    - Cecil Smith, 4/20/93 (Box 11, Folder A)
    - Mrs. Colin A. Campbell, 4/22/93 (Box 11, Folder A)
    - Mrs. Colin A. Campbell, 4/22/93 (Box 11, Folder B)
    - Oscar Wright, 4/23/93 (Box 11, Folder B)
    - Don and Andrina Phillips, 4/23/93 (Box 11, Folder B)
    - Fred Fisher, 4/23/93 (Box 11, Folder B)
    - Era Fisher, 4/23/93 (Box 11, Folder B)
    - Adrienne Luraschi, 5/3/93 (Box 12, Folder A)
    - Illegible Heston, 5/3/93 (Box 12, Folder A)
    - David Shaw, 5/5/93 (Box 12, Folder A)
    - David Shaw (Box 12, Folder B)
    - Alice Coe, 5/6/93 (Box 12, Folder B)
    - Joyce Coe, 4/24/92, 5/5/93, 5/12/93 (Box JC1, Folder A)
    - Alice Coe, Dominick Dunne, 4/17/92 (Box JC1, Folder B)
    - Delbert Mann, 4/30/93 (Box 13, Folder A)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 13, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 14, Folder A)
    - Bo Goldman, 5/28/93 (Box 14, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 15, Folder A)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 15, Folder B)
    - Phyllis Jenkins, 5/24/93 (Box 16, Folder A)
    - George Jenkins, 5/24/93 (Box 16, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 17, Folder A)
    - Charles Wickenberg, 11/12/93 (Box 17, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 18, Folder A)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 18, Folder B)
    - Bob Costello, 6/18/93 (Box 19, Folder A)
    - Bob Costello, 6/18/93 (Box 19, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 20, Folder A)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 20, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 21, Folder A)
    - Bob Ginna, 8/14/93 (Box 21, Folder B)
    - Delbert Mann, 8/23/93 (Box 21, Folder B)
    - Martin Jurow, 9/28/93 (Box 21, Folder B)
    - Max Souby, 6/8/93 (Box 22, Folder A)
    - Yvette Schumer, 2/7/94 (Box 22, Folder A)
    - Charles Cappleman, 2/8/94 (Box 22, Folder A)
    - Porter Van Zandt, 2/10/94 (Box 22, Folder A)
    - Porter Van Zandt, 2/10/94 (Box 22, Folder B)
    - No Number-A Eleanor Cogbill, Pat Weaver, 4/10/92 (Box 22, Folder B)
    - No Number-B David Shaw, 3/26/92 (Box 22, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out, 6/6/93 (Box 23, Folder A)
    - Robert Butler, 2/11/94 (Box 23, Folder B)
    - Roger Hirson [?], 2/14/94 (Box 23, Folder B)
    - Arthur Cantor 6/20/93 (something about Bill Nichols) (Box 24, Folder A)
    - Bill Nichols, 6/22/93 (Box 24, Folder B)
    - Jan (Monkhouse) Jessel, 8/14/93 (Box 25, Folder A)
    - Jan (Monkhouse) Jessel, 8/14/93 (Box 25, Folder B)
    - Jeanne Bodfish, 9/2/93 (Box 26, Folder A)
    - J. P. Miller, 10/22/93 (Box 26, Folder A)
    - Rod Steiger, 10/23/93 (Box 26, Folder B)
    - Dick Smith, 10/23/93 (Box 26, Folder B)
    - Arthur Penn, 10/26/93 (Box 26, Folder B)
    - Name Scratched Out, 2/2/94 (Box 27, Folder A)
    - Jane Arthur, 6/23/93 (Box 27, Folder B)
    - Jane Arthur 6/23/93 (part II) (Box 28, Folder A)
    - Eleanor Cogbill, 6/23/93 (Box 28, Folder A)
    - Joyce Coe, 6/23/93 (Box 28, Folder A)
    - Joyce Coe 6/23/93 (Part II) (Box 28, Folder A)
    - Sam Hall, 10/21/93 (Box 28, Folder A)
    - Tad Mosel, 10/22/93 (Box 28, Folder A)
    - (Has List of Car- era 50 People) (Box 28, Folder A)
    - Morton Foote, 7/19/93 (Box 29, Folder A)
    - Arthur Penn, 7/20/93 (Box 29, Folder A)
    - Tad Mosel 7/20/93 (continued on #30) (Box 29, Folder B)
    - Names Scratched Out (Box 30, Folder A)
    - Caroline Judson, 11/10/93 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - Albert Eggerton, 11/11/93 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - Vera (Bihari) Roukos, 11/11/93 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - David Bishop, 11/12/93 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - Pat Weaver, 9/28/93 (Box 31, Folder A)
    - Ann Levack, 9/29/93 (Box 31, Folder A)
    - Ann Levack, 9/29/93 (Box 31, Folder B)
    - David Swift, 10/1/93 (Box 32, Folder A)
    - Mike Dann, 10/4/93 (Box 32, Folder A)
    - Delbert Mann, 10/6/93 (Box 32, Folder A)
    - Delbert Mann, 10/6/93 (Box 32, Folder B)
    - Delbert Mann, 10/19/93 (Box 33, Folder A)
    - Bill Klages, 10/19/93 (Box 33, Folder A)
    - Clack Jones, 10/20/93 (Box 33, Folder B)
    - Bill Klages, 10/20/93 (Box 33, Folder B)
    - Sam Hall, 10/21/93 (Box 33, Folder B)
    - Alice, 8/30/93 (Box 34, Folder A)
    - Alice, 8/31/93 (Box 34, Folder A)
    - Kate Wells, 8/31/93 (Box 34, Folder B)
    - Alice Coe, 9/2/93 (Box 34, Folder B)
    - Jo Brown, 10/27/93 (Box 11, Folder 35-A)
    - Alvin Cooperman, 2/10/94 (Box 11, Folder 35-B)
    - Adri Butler, 2/11/94 (Box 11, Folder 35-B)
    - Ethel Winant, 10/12/93 (Box 11, Folder 36-A)
    - Melville Bernstein, 10/23/93 (Box 11, Folder 36-A)
    - Henry Bluestone, 10/23/93 (Box 11, Folder 36-A)
    - Arthur Actscyul [?], 10/28/93 (Box 11, Folder 36-A)
    - Robert Bullock, 10/29/93 (Box 11, Folder 36-A)
    - A. E. Hotchner, 10/29/93 (Box 11, Folder 36-A)
    - David Swift, 3/9/94 (Box 11, Folder 36-B)
    - Ann Nuson [?], 3/14/94 (Box 11, Folder 36-B)
    - Bill Nichols, 3/16/94 (Box 11, Folder 36-B)
    - Tad Mosel, 7/26/94 (Box 11, Folder 36-B)
    - N. Richard Nash, 10/30/93 (Box 11, Folder 37-A)
    - David Shaw, 10/30/93 (Box 11, Folder 37-A)
    - J. P. Miller, 11/1/93 (Box 11, Folder 37-A)
    - Robert Wallsten, 11/1/93 (Box 11, Folder 37-A)
    - Allen Whitehead, 11/3/93 (Box 11, Folder 37-B)
    - Mike Dann, 11/3/93 (Box 11, Folder 37-B)
    - Anon. Woman (Columbia) (Box 11, Folder 37-B)
    - Bud Yorkin, 2/16/94 (Box 11, Folder 38-A)
    - Paul Sparer, 2/17/94 (Box 11, Folder 38-A)
    - John Frankenheimer, 2/21/94 (Box 11, Folder 38-B)
    - Porter Van Zandt, 7/27/94 (Box 11, Folder 38-B)
    - Dominick Dunne, 11/6/93 (Box 11, Folder 39-A)
    - Thomas Phipps, 11/6/93 (Box 11, Folder 39-A)
    - Eileen Heckart, 11/7/93 (Box 11, Folder 39-A)
    - Eileen Heckart, 2/2/94 (Box 11, Folder 39-B)
    - Laurie Coe, 11/7/93 (Box 11, Folder 39-B)
    - Arnold Schulman, 11/8/93 (Box 11, Folder 39-B)
    - Corrine Elikman, 11/8/93 (Box 11, Folder 39-B)
    - Herbert Swope Jr., 5/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 40-A)
    - Edward Colton 6/6/94 Part II, 6/7/94 (Box 11, Folder 40-A)
    - Bob Costello, 6/7/94 (Box 11, Folder 40-A)
    - Ethel Winant, 7/27/94 (Box 11, Folder 40-B)
    - Max _____Stein, 7/29/94 (Box 11, Folder 40-B)
    - Bill Nichols, 7/28/94 (Box 11, Folder 40-B)
    - Ronald Ribman, 7/28/94 (Box 11, Folder 40-B)
    - David Karp 2/1/94 (jump to #6) (Box 11, Folder 41-A)
    - David Swift, 1/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 41-B)
    - William Gibson, 1/28/94 (Box 11, Folder 41-B)
    - Ellen Violet 2/3/94 (cont from #2) (Box 11, Folder 42-A)
    - Nancy Marchand, 2/3/94 (Box 11, Folder 42-A)
    - Joe Harris, 2/3/94 (Box 11, Folder 42-A)
    - Alice Coe, 2/26/94 (Box 11, Folder 42-B)
    - Roger Hirson [?] 2/14/94 (from #23) (Box 11, Folder 43-A)
    - Tad Mosel, 2/14/94 (Box 11, Folder 43-A)
    - Mab Ashforth, 7/26/94 (Box 11, Folder 43-B)
    - Mike Dann, 7/26/94 (Box 11, Folder 43-B)
    - Laurie Coe-, 3/18/94 (Box 11, Folder 44-A)
    - Laurie Coe 3/18/94, 3/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 44-B)
    - Jo Brown, 3/23/94 (Box 11, Folder 45-A)
    - Arthur Penn, 7/30/94 (Box 11, Folder 45-B)
    - Peter Hunt, 7/30/94 (Box 11, Folder 45-B)
    - J. P. Miller, 7/30/94 (Box 11, Folder 45-B)
    - John Coe, 3/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 46-A)
    - John Coe, 3/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 46-B)
    - John Coe, 3/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 47-A)
    - John Coe, 3/20/94 (Box 11, Folder 47-A)
    - John Coe, 3/20/94 (Box 11, Folder 47-B)
    - Charles Coe, 4/12/94 (Box 11, Folder 48-A)
    - Hilda Parks, 4/16/94 (Box 11, Folder 48-A)
    - Jospeh Stein, 4/27/94 (Box 11, Folder 48-A)
    - Sheldon Hardwick, 4/28/94 (Box 11, Folder 48-B)
    - Alice Coe, 4/28/94 (Box 11, Folder 48-B)
    - Sam Coe, 4/29/94 (Box 11, Folder 49-A)
    - Rhoda Herrick, 5/3/94 (Box 11, Folder 49-A)
    - Alice Coe, 5/9/94 (Box 11, Folder 49-B)
    - Edward Colton, 5/10/94 (Box 11, Folder 49-B)
    - Herb Gardner, 5/11/94 (Box 11, Folder 50-A)
    - Sue Coe, 5/13/94 (Box 11, Folder 50-B)
    - Sybil Costello, 6/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 51-A)
    - Bob Costello, 6/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 51-A)
    - Ellen Violett, 6/20/94 (Box 11, Folder 51-A)
    - Ellen Violett 6/20/94 (jump #52) (Box 11, Folder 51-B)
    - Ellen Violett, 6/20/94 (Box 11, Folder 52-A)
    - Eleanor Cogbill, 6/21/94 (Box 11, Folder 52-A)
    - Sue Coe, 6/21/94 (Box 11, Folder 52-A)
    - Joe Fox, 6/22/94 (Box 11, Folder 52-B)
    - Anne Levack, 6/28/94 (Box 11, Folder 52-B)
    - Harry Mark Petrakis, 8/3/94 (Box 11, Folder 52-B)
    - Vera C. Dawes 6/9/94 (W/Christine Jones) (Box 11, Folder 53-A)
    - Blank (Box 11, Folder 53-B)
    - Vera C. Dawes 6/27/94 (With Christine Jones) (Box 11, Folder 54-A)
    - Vera C. Dawes, 6/24/94 (Box 11, Folder 54-B)
    - No label (Box 11, Folder 55-A)
    - Vera C. Dawes, 7/29/94 (Box 11, Folder 55-B)
    - Barbara Schultz, 8/1/94 (Box 11, Folder 56-A)
    - Margaret Ginna, 8/3/94 (Box 11, Folder 56-B)
    - Joe Harris, 8/4/94 (Box 11, Folder 56-B)
    - Paul Bogart, 8/5/94 (Box 11, Folder 56-B)
    - Ronald Ribman, 8/6/94 (Box 11, Folder 57-A)
    - Nelle (Hasen)Jeankinson 8/6/94 (?) (Box 11, Folder 57-A)
    - Ivan Dixon, 8/9/94 (Box 11, Folder 57-A)
    - Barbara Dello Joio, 8/10/94 (Box 11, Folder 57-A)
    - Barbara Dello Joio, 8/10/94 (Box 11, Folder 57-B)
    - (from #59) Bill Weylock, 11/9/94 (Box 11, Folder 57-B)
    - Delbert Mann, 8/13/94 (Box 11, Folder 58-A)
    - Adrienne Luraschi, 8/15/94 (Box 11, Folder 58-A)
    - Bob Costello 9/8/94- Don’t Transcribe (Box 11, Folder 58-A)
    - Susan Vereker, 9/12/94 (Box 11, Folder 58-A)
    - Roger Hirson [?] 9/12/94- Don’t Transcribe (Box 11, Folder 58-A)
    - 58-B Arnold Schulman, 9/14/94 (Box 11, Folder 58-A)
    - Adeline Garner Shell, 9/20/94 (Box 11, Folder 58-A)
    - Eileen Heckart, 9/25/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - Douglas Ran, 10/14/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - Shaun Considine, 10/15/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - Jerry Chester, 10/18/95 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - George W. George, 11/7/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - Barbara Straus, 11/7/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - A. E. Hotchner, 11/8/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - Harvey Jacobs, 11/8/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-A)
    - Alice Coe, 11/8/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-B)
    - Dr. Ronald W. Busuttil, 11/8/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-B)
    - Eleanor Cogbill, 11/9/94 (Box 11, Folder 59-B)
    - Bill Weylock 11/9/94 (Jumps to #57) (Box 11, Folder 59-B)
    - Ray Katz, 11/9/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - Helen Buss Samples, 11/12/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - Ruth (Hillis) Kieller, 11/12/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - Robert Sunday, 11/13/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - 60-B Arthur Storch, 11/14/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - Delbert Mann, 11/14/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - O. (Orland) Tamburri (Don’t Transcribe) (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - end of Alice 4/28/94 interview (Box 11, Folder 61-A)
    - Ron Simon, 11/15/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - Virginia Kassel, 11/17/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - Dan Einstein, 11/17/94 (Box 11, Folder 60-A)
    - Ed Wittstein 11/18/94 (Don’t Transcribe) (Box 11, Folder 61-B)
    - Paul Aaron, 11/18/94 (Box 11, Folder 61-B)
    - Priscilla Morgan, 12/19/94 (Box 11, Folder 62-A)
    - New, Vandy Pac Bell Spokesman (Box 11, Folder 62-B)
    - Margaret Sheffield, 1/19/95 (Box 11, Folder 62-B)
    - Betty J. Stevens, 2/7/95 (Box 11, Folder 62-B)
    - Stanley Oran, 2/8/95 (Box 11, Folder 62-B)
    - Elizabeth Brockman, 3/3/95 (Box 11, Folder 63-A)
    - Patricia (Naney) Enrler 3/4/95 [?] (Box 11, Folder 63-A)
    - Milt Myers, 5/21/95 (Box 11, Folder 63-A)
    - Walter Bernstein, 11/15/95 (Box 11, Folder 63-B)
    - Priscilla Morgan Msg., 1/14/96 (Box 11, Folder 63-B)
    - Laurie Coe 2/14/96 Msg. (Box 11, Folder 63-B)
    - 64-A Martha (Menun) Carpenter, 4/10/95 (Box 11, Folder 63-B)
    - Ethel (Wildermuth) Grover, 4/11/95 (Box 11, Folder 63-B)
    - Elizabeth (Creswick) Shiflett, 4/11/95 (Box 11, Folder 63-B)
    - Patty Duke, 4/13/95 (Box 11, Folder 63-B)
    - Don Petersen 4/18/95 (ship ‘copy of show’ Stuff) (Box 11, Folder 64-B)
    - Mayo Simon, 4/25/95 (Box 11, Folder 64-B)
    - Joyce Coe, 4/26/95 (Box 11, Folder 64-B)
    - Joyce Coe, 4/26/95 (Box 11, Folder 65-A)
    - no label (Box 11, Folder 65-B)
    - FC UCLA Tribute, 8/2/00 (Box 11, Folder 65-B)